Guide to the Miriam Salpeter papers, 1952-2003
Salpeter, Miriam papers, 1952-2003
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Miriam Salpeter papers, 1952-2003
21-45-3315
Miriam M. Salpeter
2 cubic ft.
Correspondence, publications, course material, grant applications and audiocassette tapes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, publications, course material, grant applications and audiocassette tapes related to Salpeter's career in the Dept. of Neurobiology and Behavior.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of Neurobiology and Behavior, Cornell University from 1973-2000.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, publications, course material, grant applications and audiocassette tapes related to Salpeter's career in the Dept. of Neurobiology and Behavior.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Salpeter, M.M. (Miriam M.); Cornell University--Faculty.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Dept. of Neurobiology and Behavior.
Subjects:
Neurobiology.; Molecular neurobiology.; Molecular biology.
Form and Genre Terms:
Audiocassettes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Reprints, 1952-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Reprints, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Reprints, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Reprints, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Reprints, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Reprints, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Reprints, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Reprints, 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Reprints, 1996-2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Abstracts for Meetings, 1971-2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Electron Scattering Calculations, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Mask Analysis - Calculations, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Auto-Radiography - Resolution, Before 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Auto-Radiography - Calculations, Papers, After 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Auto-Radiography - Unpublished Paper and Calculations (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Book Reviews and Other Papers, 1985-2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Biographical Material (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Biology 320 Lecture Notes (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Lecture Notes, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Course Materials - 720 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Course Materials - 325, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, Paper -Dementia, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Course Materials - BioNB 420 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Course Materials - BioNB 420, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Course Materials - BioNB 222, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Course Materials - BioSci 498, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Course Materials - BioNB 496 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Radiography Lab Notes (Box 1, Folder 28)
- NIH Applications, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- NIH Grant Applications, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- NIH Grant Applications, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- NIH Grant Applications, 1960s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 32)
- NIH Grant Applications, 1970s-2002 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- NIH Grant Applications, 1969-1998 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- BioNB 420-2 Clinical Aspects of Neurobiology Course Packet, Fall 1997 (Box 1)
- BioNB 420-3 Clinical Aspects of Neurobiology Course Packet, Fall 1998 (Box 1)
- Cornell Theory Center Publication Discovery, 1993 (Box 1)
- Grant Applications, 1971-1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Grant Applications, 1970-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Grant Applications, 1979-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Curriculum Vitae, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1991-2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Correspondence with Luis Bachmann and Kodak, 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Journal Submissions and Receiver's Comments, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Correspondence re: Awards and Marcus Singer Symposium, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Glossy Unsorted Prints (Box 2)
- Cassette Tape - BioSci 222, Richard Harris-Warrick, Synapses and Neural Integrations, Feb. 22, 1991 (Box 2)
- Cassette Tape - BioSci 222, Richard Harris- Warrick, Excitation and Inhibition, Feb. 25, 1991 (Box 2)
- Cassette Tape - BioSci 222, Richard Harris-Warrick, Release of Neurotransmitters, Feb. 27, 1991 (Box 2)
- Cassette Tape - BioSci 222, Richard Harris-Warrick, Synapses, Feb. 10, 1992 (Box 2)
- Cassette Tape - BioSci 222, Richard Harris-Warrick, Ionic Mechs Excitation and Inhibition, Feb. 12, 1992 (Box 2)
- Cassette Tape - BioSci 222, Richard Harris-Warrick, Neurotransmitters Release, Feb. 14, 1992 (Box 2)